Hello hello everyone how are you all I am
your own Vishal Aakash Amit Raj Sharma and
you are watching this real Before starting today's video I want to
thank you so much
because you have asked a question related to cyber insurance for the first time on the channel
Background of Aastha Insurance Company
Life Insurance Health Insurance ULIP
Plan I have been asking similar questions
but this is the first time that you have
asked about Cyber ​​Insurance so
thank you very much without wasting time let us know what is Cyber
Insurance in very simple
words let me tell you an
insurance policy which provides you financial protection against cyber crime
you will call that policy Fiber
Insurance what
news do you get in it first of all comes identity
theft now nowadays people also keep a lock in
which their documents etc are kept
if it gets stolen from there if some
cyber criminal does something like this
then the account comes under identity theft
other things also come under it
like your social media profile if you have any lock
there you will have dominance over it too
right apart from this as soon as you
You use banking, credit card, debit
card for online transactions, you
use e-wallet, there a cyber
criminal can steal your files, that too
you get blind cover in it.
Apart from this, there is another thing called cyber stalking, what is
done in it,
a cyber criminal will keep an eye on your profile
and will keep
spiking here, sometimes it also happens that if
you post something else there, then something else gets
posted there, due to which you will suffer financial
loss, it can tarnish your image there,
so this type of
ingredient comes under cyber stalking,
that too is under cover in it, then
comes your IT Patpai Tap,
like your documents, which
document, if you have created something
like recording etc., you do rights
or you have created some property
online or apart from this, if you have online sites,
that also increases your ID, the
rest of your malware
is covered, so you must be aware that when it is
spared  It
destroys a lot of things inside your system inside the mobile,
you all know about this fitting completely,
nowadays because emails come in this
type of fat or some link comes from where
your money can be lost and your personal
data can also be lost, then next comes
your cyber extra mission, now
extra mission, you know that
someone is forcibly taking money from you, now if you have a
business or you are doing business online, then
someone has stolen your data and has
completely compromised your computer system, he is
asking for money from you, right, make your demand,
until you fulfill his demand, he is
not willing to give you back access, so
this comes under cyber extension, now
apart from this, there are many other things too, Rajender
covers because today's insurance companies
also give the opportunity to modify the product according to the sleep of an individual, this business person's recording,
so
it will depend on your questions,
as your questions come, we will keep knowing about many things
in detail later,
if you want to read about it,
you will find the link in the description,
right, join the Telegram channel
because there  But I keep sharing PDFs etc.
and I told one thing about a product to
others and understood it myself, there
is good insurance protection, I
never take the production incomplete,
thank you very much, thank you very much brother.